我 你 小蛋糕们都准备好了
Well, you, me, and the cupcakes are ready,
就等人上门了
now, we just need people.
快看
Ooh, here we go!
那女的看上去可能会进来呢
This one looks like she might come in.
走你妹啊 丑女
Yeah, keep walking, ugly!
丑女 她就像一个超模呢
Ugly? She's like a supermodel.
那她有没有进来买东西呀
Did she come in and buy something?
-没有 -那她就是丑女一个
- No. - Then, she ugly.
好吧 虽然现在小蛋糕滞销
Okay, yes, business is slow,
但我们没必要没品又毒舌吧
but we don't have to drop to that level.
哇 那个男的肯定会进来的
Ooh, this guy is definitely coming in.
走你妹啊 死胖子
Keep walking, fatty!
他还是个丑男
And he ugly.
欢迎光临麦克斯自制小蛋糕店
Welcome to Max's homemade cupcakes!
你们好呀 小蛋糕多少钱一个
Hello. How much are your cupcakes?
算了
No.
婊子
Whore.
倒霉鬼 你要请我喝可乐
Jinx, you owe me a coke!
咱俩异口同声叫那位老太太婊子
We both called an old lady a whore.
对啊 咱俩完全同步
I know! We are in complete sync.
这对我们的生意是一大利好啊
That is so good for business.
3块钱卖我一个
I'll give you $3.
抱歉 但明码标价是4块钱
I'm sorry, they're $4.
这里一个客人都没有 我愿意买你们就该偷笑了
there's no one in here. You'll take what you get.
我爱上那个婊子了
I'm in love with that whore.
你好 我是麦克斯自制小蛋糕店
Hello. I'm calling from Max's homemade cupcakes
来跟您介绍我们的"相约早晨"特别活动
to acquaint you with our new "Mornings with Max's" special.
不 先生 特别活动不是那种事
No, sir, that is not what our special is.
而且那事我都还没跟我男人"做"过呢
And I haven't even done that with my boyfriend yet,
所以请放尊重点
so don't be rude.
把电话给我
Give me that phone.
你又胖又丑 你个死猪扒
Ya fat, ya ugly, ya fugly.
麦克斯 我们得多找点生意
Max, we have got to get more business going.
苏菲给我们开店的钱
The money Sophie gave us to open the shop
只够交下个月的租金了
will only cover next month's rent.
等等 下个月的租金我们都有啦
Wait, we already have next month's rent?
那还有什么可担心的
Why are we worried?
我们已经比随便一个美国人都好多了
We're doing better than everyone else in America.
瞧瞧 这不是白马王子[帅哥王子]吗
Well, well, well, if it isn't Prince Charming.
厄尔 王子真的是帅哥吗
But, Earl, is prince charming,
还是他只是个穿紫衣的娘炮啊
or is he just a diva in purple?
好兴奋 厄尔给我起绰号了
So psyched. Finally got a personalized hello from Earl.
他叫我白马王子
He called me Prince Charming.
我融入你们了 宝贝 成一份子了
I'm in, baby, I am in.
是我就不会太高兴
I wouldn't get too excited.
他很可能只是忘记你的名字了
He probably just forgot your name.
所有进餐馆的波多黎各人他都叫"森巴舞男"
He calls every Puerto Rican guy that comes in here "La bamba."
麦克斯自制小蛋糕店
Max's homemade cupcakes.
好 我等着
Yes, I'll hold.
我们当然有无糖和无麸的啦
Of course we do sugar-free and gluten-free.
我马上回来 我得先接个电话
I'll be right back, I just gotta take this call.
我知道 但那糖尿病是多严重呢
I understand, but, like, how diabetic?
我感觉有点恶心想吐
I feel a little sick to my stomach.
怎么会 你都还没吃过这里的东西呢
Why? You haven't even eaten here yet.
不 我是紧张啦
No, I'm nervous.
我是来这里跟卡洛琳说件大事的
I came here to tell caroline something kind of big.
什么事 你秘密在长岛有妻有儿了吗
What? You have a secret family on Long Island?
-不是 -你患有丙型肝炎吗 还是丁型？
- No. you have hep-c? "D"?
-新型肝炎的一种吗 -不是
- One of the new heps? - No.
我没有任何肝炎
I don't have any of the heps.
现在感觉对她说"我爱她"
Now, telling her I'm in love with her
这句话会很无趣吧
is just going to sound boring.
你要告诉她你爱她啊
You're gonna tell her you love her?
在这个破餐馆表白啊
Here in the diner?
为什么 垃圾场关门了吗
Why, was the dump closed?
森巴舞男 再多弄点咖啡
Hey, we need more coffee, La Bamba.
安迪 这里不适合跟人说"我爱你"
Andy, this isn't where you tell someone "I love you."
这里适合跟人说他们的变性手术还过得去
This is where you tell someone their sex change looks passable.
这有什么大不了的
What's the big deal?
如果有感觉 为何不能直说呢
If I feel it, why shouldn't I say it?
我觉得她一定会欣喜万分
I think she'd be all over that.
不可能 如果这个情节没有出现在
Nope. If it didn't happen to Kate Hudson
某个由凯特·哈德森主演的白痴爱情喜剧里
in some stupid romantic comedy,
那对卡洛琳也是完全无效
then it won't work for Caroline.
抱歉 你说啥
Sorry, what?
你说话的时候 我灵魂出窍
I left and went into another theater in my mind
去看了别的电影了
while you were talking.
我知道 这很恶心 但她就爱这些
I know, it's so creepy, but she likes it.
真的 如果你能在情人节那天
Really, if you could arrange for it to rain,
安排一场倾盆大雨 或是在雨中一路追她
or run after her to the airport in the rain,
追到机场 结果两人却双双出现在
but somehow end up on top of the empire state building
帝国大厦的楼顶上 那就最好不过啦
on valentine's day, that'd be best.
我刚卖掉三打小蛋糕
Well, I just sold three dozen cupcakes,
我们只需在其中一个盒子上写着"无糖"就行了
we just have to mark "No sugar" on one of the boxes.
你有什么话要对我说吗
So what did you want to say to me?
没什么 我就过来打个招呼
No, nothing, just came by to say hi.
我得回去下载几部电影看看了
I gotta go download a couple movies.
奥列格 我的菜呢
Hey, Oleg. Where's my food?
你要的起司汉堡和薯条 上菜吧
Cheeseburger with fries, pick-up.
阿憨 你在窗子里面显得真高啊
Han, you look so tall in the window.
说实话 你踩在另一个小矮人的肩膀上了吗
Tell me the truth, are you standing on another tiny person?
才没有
No.
我踩的是箱子
On the box.
奥列格不得不请假
Oleg had to leave.
苏菲从波兰回来了
Sophie came back from her trip to Poland,
他很担心她 因为她情绪非常非常低落
and he's worried, 'cause she's very, very depressed.
为什么 她也看见你戴发网的蠢样了吗
Why, did she see you in that hair net?
才不是呢 苏菲飞回去看她的新房子
Come on, listen, when Sophie went to see her new house,
可那里根本没房子
there was no house.
她的波兰承包商骗光了她的钱
Her Polish contractor ripped off her money.
可怜的苏菲 真为她感到难过
Poor Sophie. I feel terrible.
我知道被人骗是什么感觉
I know what it feels like to be ripped off.
有次我买了芬迪的名牌包 回家往里衬一看
I once bought a Fendi purse, but when I looked inside,
上面写着"分迪"
it said "Rendi."
哪个无良的神会让这种事发生啊
What kind of god would let that happen?
麦克斯 我拿了个山寨包去派对呢
Max, I went to a party with that.
我们应该下班后去探望她
We should stop by after work, see how she is,
再带几个她最爱吃的小蛋糕
and bring her some of her favorite cupcakes.
或是你可以还她借你们的2万块钱
Or you could give her that $20,000 she loaned you.
借我们 苏菲是把那笔钱当礼物送给我们
Loaned us? Sophie gave us that money as a gift.
反正我听到的不是这样 快上菜
Not what I hear. Pick-up!
对了 我们做不了意大利面了 没番茄酱了
And we're out of spaghetti. There's no sauce.
不可能 我们有好多番茄酱呢
No, han, there's plenty of sauce.
我知道 但我够不着那个架子
I know, but I can't reach the shelf.
你确定那钱是苏菲作为礼物送给我们的吗
Hey, are we sure that money Sophie gave us was a gift?
当然 表示她支持我们的梦想
Yes. She gave it to us to support our dream.
我懂的 我有钱的时候 我都会无偿送出去
I know when I had money, I gave it out freely,
而且从未期望对方有所回报
and never expected anything in return.
比如我把那个漂亮的"分迪"包送给我女仆
Like when I gave my maid that gorgeous rendi.
我不了解不求回报的人的心态
Well, I don't know about people not expecting stuff back.
有一次 一个男的给我买了一杯冰沙
One time, a guy bought me a slushy,
接下来的三周 我成了他的人
and for the next three weeks, he owned me.
不是说笑的 他是真正地拥有我
No, he really owned me.
八天后 我差点被卖个一个卡车司机
Eight days in, I almost got traded to a trucker.
我甚至不会提到她的礼物
And I wouldn't even mention her gift.
还钱只会像羞辱她 我保证
It will only insult her, and I promise,
没人指望我们把钱还给她
nobody is expecting us to give the money back.
进来吧 姑娘们 支票带了吗
Come in, girls. Did you bring the check?
没带 那是她送我们的礼物 大礼
No, because it was a gift-a big-ass gift,
但我们带来我们的爱和小蛋糕
but we brought our love and we brought cupcakes.
我怀疑她是否会吃
Well, I doubt she'll eat them.
她连她的高丽菜汤都一口没喝
She hasn't even touched her kapusniak,
那还是专门给被承包商欺诈的
which is the dish traditionally served to polish women
波兰女人吃的传统菜肴呢
who have been wronged by their contractors.
这个习俗还真明确啊
Such a specific culture.
那还不是最糟的事情
But that's not the worst thing.
她非常低落 毫无性致
She is so depressed, no sex,
这对我来说可是个大难题
which is big problem for me,
因为我觉得抑郁的女人非常性感
because I find depressed women very hot.
很多男人都这样
A lot of guys do.
不然我为什么六年来喝酒都没掏过一分钱
Why do you think I haven't paid for a drink in six years?
我进去告诉她你们来了
I'll go in and tell her you're here.
她就这么躺在床上
She's just lying there on the bed, lifeless, hot...
死气沉沉 风情万种
lifeless, hot...
性感撩人
The big tease.
苏菲 你借钱给她们的那俩妞
Sophie, the two girls who you loaned the money to
来看你了
are here to see you.
都说了是礼物
It was a gift.
非常慷慨大方 但还是礼物
A generous, generous gift, but still a gift.
我们真的确定吗
Are we sure about that?
我当了冰沙男孩的玩物三周呢
'cause I was slushy boy's bitch for three weeks,
我当时"奉献"的哦
and I did things.
瞧 麦克斯给你带了小蛋糕
Look, Max brought you cupcakes,
你最喜欢的口味 香草加培根碎末
your favorite: vanilla with a bacon fat drizzle.
不 我被人背叛时吃不了东西
No, I can't eat when I've been betrayed.
再说一次什么口味
What kind again?
苏菲 我是一个有耐心的男人
Sophie, I am patient man,
但我同时也是一个饥渴的男人
but I am also horny man.
你什么时候能摆脱这种负面情绪啊
Any idea when you will snap out of this?
你何不现在就拉开拉链 爬到我身上
Oh, why don't you just unzip and climb on top of me now
赶紧搞完了事呢
and get it over with?
-不要了吧 -我们该走了
- Oh, no. - Well, we should be going.
别走 姑娘们 留下来
No, girls, stay.
她要是都不挣扎 那还有什么乐趣啊
If she's not even going to put up a fight, what's the fun?
真的不吃吗
Are you sure?
培根末哦 天堂的味道
Bacon drizzle, little bit of heaven.
不 我不想吃
No, I don't want them.
好吧 那我把小蛋糕放这里
Okay, let's put the cupcakes here,
以防你改变主意想吃
in case you change your mind.
这是一把枪吗
Is this a gun?
是的 我才不要用刀捅死自己呢
Yes. I'm not going to stab myself to death.
你知道这外套值多少钱吗
Do you know how much this outfit costs?
苏菲 你一定会挺过来的
Sophie, you're going to get through this.
对了 你穿黑色美呆了
And by the way, you look amazing in black.
现在我的心情不想穿亮色
Oh, well, no more bright colors for me now.
哀悼期间只穿丧服黑
I'm in mourning.
瞧 黑色胸罩 黑色吊袜带
See? Black bra, black garters,
还有 黑色内裤
and look, black panties.
可你没有穿内裤啊
Um, you're not wearing any panties.
没有吗
I'm not?
抱歉让你看见下面那堆茂盛的杂草了
I'm sorry about that wild mess down there.
苏菲 你被人骗我也感到难过
Sophie, I feel bad you got ripped off.
这是我今晚赚的小费 一共27块
Here are all my tips from tonight: $27.
八小时就赚这么点啊
For eight hours?
好吧 现在我替你感到难过了
Oh, now, I'm depressed for you.
你想借用我的枪吗
You want to borrow my gun?
我觉得你只需要吃点东西
You know what? I think you just need to eat something,
很快 你就能恢复到原来的样子了
And pretty soon, you'll be back to your old self:
一个乐善好施 不求回报的女人
A woman who gives gifts and expects nothing in return,
因为礼物的定义正是如此
'cause that's what a gift is.
苏菲 那有让你感觉爽点吗
Sophie, is that doing anything for you?
反正我也不反感啊
Yeah, well, I'm not hating it.
这汤闻起来味道不错
Here, this soup smells amazing.
不要 我没有力气吃东西
Oh, no. I don't have the energy to eat.
苏菲 张开嘴 放进去
Sophie, open your mouth and put this in.
拜托 你这样就跟奥列格一样坏了
Oh, come on. Now you're as bad as Oleg.
乖了 好点没
There. Better?
汤冷死了
That's cold.
苏菲 只要你开口 银行我都帮你抢
Sophie, just say the word, and I will rob a bank for you.
苏菲 我知道你很受伤
Sophie, I understand you're hurting,
但我们几乎把钱都花在那家店上了
but we've already spent most of the money on the shop,
而且现在生意也不好
and business just isn't good.
不是钱的问题
It's not the money.
大家都觉得是钱的问题
Everybody thinks it's the money.
远不止如此
It's more than that.
我的湖边小屋是我的梦想 我失去的是梦想
My lake house was my dream, and I lost my dream.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God!
能搞清这点就太好了
Well, I'm glad that's cleared up.
不是钱的问题
Not about the money.
麦克斯 走吧 她受惊吓了
Max, come on, she's had a shock,
我们应该让她好好睡觉
we should let her sleep.
你们俩真幸运 梦想还没破碎
You girls are so lucky. You still have your dream.
苏菲 你也成为我们梦想的一份子呢
Well, Sophie, what if you were part of our dream?
什么 谁的梦想
I'm sorry? Whose dream?
我们的梦想
Our dream.
你们的梦想 小蛋糕在哪里
Your dream? Where's that cupcake?
苏菲给了那笔钱 我们才能开成小蛋糕店
Look, Sophie's the only reason we have a shop.
我们应该...让她当合伙人
We should make her, like, a partner.
合伙人
Partner!
但咱们已经是合伙人了
But you and I are already partners.
我觉得已经有点人满为患了吧
I feel like we're kind of partnered out.
不然就当静默合伙人好了
What about a silent partner?
静默合伙人 我喜欢
Silent partner! Yeah, I like that.
我的食欲都开始恢复了
I'm getting my appetite back,
连性欲都回来了
and also, my sex drive.
要走要留 随便你俩 反正老子是要上了
Go or stay, girls. Either way, I'm going in.
抱歉我说可以让苏菲成为蛋糕店的合伙人
I'm sorry I said Sophie could be part of the store.
我只是为她感到难过
I just felt bad for her,
躺在床上 全身黑衣
lying there, all in black,
悲伤到都没心情打理"小妹妹"了
too sad to even make her junk pretty.
没关系啦
It's fine.
"静默合伙人"只是个挂名职位
"Silent partner" is just a figurehead role anyway,
而且知道你有如此善心也挺好的
and it's nice to know you have such a big heart.
这不是我的本心
It's not my heart.
看到那团东西后改变了我的心
What I saw down there changed me.
那看起来就像是动物为了过冬
It looks like something an animal built
而造的避寒兽穴
to live in for the winter.
慢着 苏菲的大吊灯在这里干嘛
Wait, what is Sophie's chandelier doing here?
这是波兰版的入侵民宅吗
Is this the polish version of a home invasion?
闯进去然后留下点俗气的东西
They break in and leave something tacky?
早上好 合伙人们
Good morning, partners.
我不知道着装要求 所以我就穿了商务便装
I didn't know the dress code, so I went business casual.
瞧 我为我的湖边小屋买的大吊灯
Look, the chandelier that I bought for my lake house.
现在我们的梦想合二为一了
Oh, now our dreams are together.
苏菲 这跟我们原来的风格大相径庭
Sophie, it's not the look we were going for.
我知道 好看多了 对吧
Oh, I know. Much better, right?
这绝对不是我们的风格
That is definitely not our style.
这里像被蒂姆·波顿的诡异电影横扫过一样
It looks like a Tim Burton movie just spit up in here.
我觉得还挺漂亮的啊
I think it's kind of pretty.
但我懂屁啊
But what do I know?
我有次把仅有的50块拿去买青蛙彩陶罐
I once spent my last 50 bucks on a frog pinata.
忍不住想买啊
Had to have it.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕店
Max's homemade cupcakes.
对 我们是一家上档次的蛋糕店
Yes, we're an upscale bakery, and--
现在我们还卖何奇三明治哦
Now, we sell hoagies.
不不不 先生 我们不卖何奇三明治
Oh, no, no, no, sir, we do not sell hoagies.
不 我们卖
Yes, we do.
你想要多少 我去拿笔记一下
How many would you like? Let me get a pen.
怎么了
What's happening?
你终于要来说卡洛琳的坏话了吗
Are we finally gonna trash Caroline?
不 我需要你的帮忙
No, I need your help.
我连续不断地看了四部爱情烂片
I watched four chick flicks back-to-back,
想出了几个告诉
then I made a list of possible ways
卡洛琳我爱她的可行办法
to tell Caroline I love her.
我本来还想多列几个 但我看得月经都来了
I was gonna make more, but I got my period.
好的 把你的选项都跟我说一遍
Okay, run the choices past me.
哪一个让我听了最想吐
Whichever one makes me want to hurl the most,
就是最佳的选择了
that's your winner.
我可以在她公寓外放歌
I could play a song for her outside of her apartment,
不过都2012年了 大手提收音机很难找
but keep in mind how hard it is to find a boom box in 2012.
对啊 而且如果你在我们公寓外面搞这个
Yeah, plus, if you do that outside our apartment,
你会被我...
you'll be shot.
乱抢射死
by me.
好吧 那在中央公园的溜冰场
Okay, what about sharing cocoa and a hot dog
俩人共喝热可可 共享热狗时呢
on the ice rink in central park?
行 就这个
Yup, that's it.
让我想把自己的脑袋扯下来
Makes me want to take my head off
然后扔到大街上去
and throw it into the street.
很好 对了 麦克斯
Cool. Oh, and, Max,
我觉得我是地球上唯一能区别
I think I'm the only straight guy on earth
迪伦·麦克德莫特与
who knows the difference between Dylan Mcdermott and
德蒙特·莫罗尼的直男了
Dermott Mulroney,
而朋友 这就是爱啊
and that, my friend, is love.
这是什么狗屁味道
Oh, what's that funky-ass smell?
出意大利香肠味的除臭剂了吗
Do they finally sell pepperoni febreze?
麦克斯 这样完全不行
Max, this already isn't working.
臭哄哄的蒜味香肠 艳俗的大吊灯
The stinky salami, the gaudy chandelier?
这就像一家闹鬼的快餐店
It's like a haunted Quiznos in here.
我让奥列格去皇后区
Hey, I'm sending Oleg to Queens
买一箱柑橘味饮料 没错
to pick up a flat of Fresca. Yeah.
冰柑橘饮料配何奇三明治
There's nothing better with a hoagie
可是最棒的组合
than an ice-cold fresca.
我就是在想着那个呢
That's what I wanted!
听着
Look...
配上腌鸡蛋风味更佳哦
they'll go great with the pickled eggs!
我的梦想正式变成了恶梦
This just went from my dream to a nightmare.
天啊 卡洛琳 真的是你
Oh, my God, Caroline! It is you!
史黛西 不是吧 毕业后我就没见过你了
Stacy, no way! I haven't seen you since graduation.
我们一起念的沃顿商学院
We went to Wharton together.
这个姑娘是个天才
This girl is a genius.
永远都是班级第一
Always top of the class.
你在这里干嘛
So what are you doing here?
坐拥世界的空挡出来买个小蛋糕吗
Buying a cupcake on your way to running the world?
不 这家店是我开的
No, I own this shop.
这家小蛋糕店是你开的啊
You own this little cupcake shop?
当然还有其他更大的店面啦
And many other bigger shops.
这是我们威廉斯堡新开的分店
This is our new Williamsburg location.
没错 我知道 那个吊灯完全不搭
And yes, I know, the chandelier is all wrong.
我跟设计师说 我们太平洋西北地区的分店
I told the designer, none of our pacific northwest locations
都不许挂这么俗气的吊灯
will have the chandeliers.
你这么厉害 25岁坐拥小蛋糕帝国很正常
Of course, you'd own a cupcake empire at 25.
-这位是麦克斯 -你好
- Oh, and this is Max. - Hi.
我刚从大西北地区分店调过来
I just transferred from our Boise location.
是什么东西这么臭啊
What's that horrible smell?
是一种叫"何奇三明治"的玩意
It's something called a "hoagie."
工人们都喜欢吃 对吧 麦克斯
The workers like them. Right, Max?
是的 谢谢你的何奇三明治[西语]
Si, gracias por la hoagie.
我得走了
Well, I have to go.
我在楼上的BBD&L公司做顾问
I'm consulting upstairs at BBD&L.
-楼上啊 -对啊
- Oh, upstairs. - Yeah.
就知道你一定会东山再起
Always knew you'd land on your feet.
有时间去喝一杯 你请客哦 大亨
Let's go for drinks, and you're paying, mogul.
希望她喜欢喝水啊
I hope she likes water.
我现在该怎么办 史黛西在这栋楼上班
Now what am I going to do? Stacy's in the building.
你可以搬去奇幻世界开一家你说的分店啊
Well, you could move to Narnia and run that branch,
你个病态的骗子
you pathological liar.
麦克斯 我不想让人们看见我这样
Max, this is not how I want people to see me,
或闻到我有这股味
or smell me, quite frankly.
我们必须摆脱蒜味香肠 大吊灯
We have to get rid of the salami, the chandelier,
还有苏菲
and the Sophie.
这是我们的梦想 不是她的
This is our dream, not hers.
好吧 我会告诉她
Okay, fine, I'll tell her.
苏菲 我们有话跟你说
Hey, Sophie, can we talk to you?
好消息 姑娘们
Good news, girls.
现在我们还卖刮刮乐哦
Now we sell scratchers.
但我有个更好的主意
But I have even a better idea.
你们俩打扮成小蛋糕
You two should dress up as big cupcakes
去外面分派免费的试吃品
and pass out free samples.
苏菲 麦克斯有话要跟你说
Sophie, Max has something she wants to say to you.
打住
Wait.
姑娘们 让我先说
Girls, I have something to say first.
两天前 我一度徘徊于自杀的边缘
Two days ago, I was on the verge of suicide.
说真的 我绝食了整整一下午呢
Yeah, seriously, I hadn't eaten all afternoon.
但你们对自己梦想的慷慨
But your generosity with your dream
给了我东山再起和打理杂"毛"的动力
has given me a reason to get up and get a wax.
是的
Yeah.
麦克斯 你刚刚想说什么来着
Max, there was something you wanted to say?
我本来是想说...
I was going to say--
你看起来真可口
You look delicious.
我简直就像甜心波波的肥婆老妈去舞会
I look like Honey Boo Boo's mom at the prom.
这太丢人了
This is so humiliating.
现在我知道超模泰拉
Now I know how Tyra felt
做节目 扮成胖子上街时的感觉了
when she went undercover as that fat person.
拜托告诉我这是我们堕落的极限了
Please tell me this is our bottom.
这是你的极限
Well, it's your bottom.
我有次去酒吧喝酒
I went to happy hour once
醒来时发现自己在布朗克斯动物园的
and woke up naked in the penguin habitat
企鹅栖息地 浑身赤裸着
at the Bronx Zoo.
还有我当年做过的"事"哦
And I did things.
姑娘们
Hey, girls.
你们俩呆站在这里干嘛
What are you two doing just standing there?
上帝给小蛋糕两条腿是有理由的
God gave cupcakes legs for a reason.
你们得走上街头
You need to hit the streets,
摇晃你们的"蛋糕" 展示你们的"好货"
shake your cake maker, and show people your goods.
别看我呀 是香草白妞不愿意
Hey, don't look at me, it's vanilla.
我还期待着走到
I was looking forward to going up
街上完全陌生的人们面前
to complete strangers on the street
大声嚷着"吃我" 但她不愿意去
and saying "eat me," but she won't leave.
如果你们不出去拉客
Well, if you're not going to go out and get the customers,
那我只好帮你们带客上门了
then I'll have to bring the customers to you.
真是什么事都得靠我做啊
I gotta do everything around here.
说真的 我不敢相信我们就在这呆站着
Seriously, I can't believe we're just standing here
我们应该在享受追着路上胖子跑
when we could be chasing fat people down the street,
对他们喊"你吃了我的兄弟"才对啊
yelling, "You ate my brother!"
瞧瞧你俩
Look at you two.
能再给我一大杯牛奶配 那就更好了
What I wouldn't give for a giant glass of milk.
瞧瞧你
Look at you, though.
看起来真可爱
You look so cute.
才没有 别看我
No, don't look at me.
穿这玩意真是丢脸死了
I'm totally embarrassed in this thing.
是啊 她又可爱又尴尬
Yes, she's cute and embarrassed,
穿着五彩缤纷站在公共场合 最适合...
in a larger-than-life, colorful, public setting.
对啊
Ah, right.
卡洛琳 听着 我想对你说...
So, Caroline, listen, I wanted to--
姑娘们 一些年轻的上班族来了
Look, girls, some young professionals.
天啊 她还把史黛西拉来了
Oh, my God! She's bringing stacy.
不能让她瞧见我穿这个
She can't see me in this.
我可是毕业典礼致词的学生代表 拿着
I was her valedictorian. Take this.
慢点
Wait.
拉我起身 麦克斯 拉我起身
Help me up, Max! Help me up!
好啊 你现在就跟我那肥妈一样
Oh, great. Now you're like my mom.
来 给我你的左手
Here, give me your left hand.
好的 再给我你的右手
Okay, give me your right hand.
快起来 掉地上五秒内捡起还能吃
Get up! Get up! Five second rule.
你们俩疯狂的小蛋糕在干嘛
What are you two crazy cakes doing?
顾客都没了 被你们吓跑了
You lost your customers. They ran away.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我真不明白
Oh, I don't get it.
你也不愿意推广何奇三明治和腌鸡蛋
You won't push the hoagies or the pickled eggs.
你肯定很害怕成功对吧
You must really have a fear of success.
至少我们躲开史黛西了
Well, at least we missed Stacy.
你知道你还躲开了什么吗 安迪
Well, you know what else you missed? Andy.
他本来打算告诉你他爱你
He was about to tell you he loves you.
什么
What?
就刚才在走廊 和在溜冰场时
Just now, in the hall, and at the ice rink.
他这一周千方百计想跟你说
He's been trying to tell you all week.
但我这周都醉心于工作
But I've been too preoccupied with work,
就像《假结婚》里的桑德拉·布洛克
Like Sandra Bullock in The Proposal.
他本来计划在溜冰场上告诉我吗
So he was gonna tell me at the ice rink?
中央公园的那个吗
The one in central park?
对啊 在你们共喝热可可 共享着热狗时
Yes, while having cocoa and splitting a hot dog.
天啊
Oh, my God!
那就是我梦想中的表白场景啊
That's, like, my dream "I love you" scenario.
为什么你不早点告诉我呢
Why didn't you tell me sooner?
因为一旦遇到其他人恶心的爱情问题
Because when it comes to other people's creepy love stuff,
我就会变成"静默"合伙人
that's when I'm a silent partner,
你也得停止沉迷那些恶心的爱情喜剧了
And you need to stop with this creepy rom-com stuff.
因为生活不像电影
Life isn't like a movie.
有时你不可能立马获得成功
Sometimes you're not a success right away,
有时你得默默咽下苦果 扮成一个小蛋糕
sometimes you have to just eat it and be a cupcake,
有时无论别人是在何时何地说"我爱你"
and sometimes you have to take your "I love you"
你都得接受
whichever way it comes.
你说得太对了
You are so right.
我不需等到完美的那一刻
I don't have to wait for the moment to be perfect,
就好像瑞茜·威瑟斯彭在《情归阿拉巴马》那样
like it was for Reese Witherspoon in Sweet Home Alabama.
我的人生不是一出爱情喜剧
My life's not a romantic comedy.
我可以用我自己的方式去做
I can do it my own way.
就好像《我最好朋友的婚礼》里的茱莉亚·罗伯茨
Like Julia Roberts in My Best Friend's Wedding.
安迪 是我
Andy, it's me!
马上出来
I'll be right out.
不 我等不及了
No, this can't wait any longer.
我不需要盛大的浪漫喜剧时刻
I don't need a big romantic comedy moment.
别进来
No--
抱歉 我以为这是办公室
Oh, sorry. I thought it was the office!
不是
Not the office.
我卡住了
I'm stuck.
我想开溜 但溜不了
Oh, I want to go, but I can't.
我以后想开拉也拉不了了
And I'll never be able to go again.
我正坐在马桶上 你正穿着蛋糕服
Well, I'm on the toilet and you're in a cupcake.
没有比这更怪的时刻了
Can't get creepier than this, so,
卡洛琳 我爱你
Caroline, I love you.
我也爱你
I love you too.
拜托 把我推出去
Oh, please, push me out.
如何 浪漫吗
How'd it go? Was it romantic?
他一边蹲马桶一边说爱我
He told me he loved me on the toilet.
天啊 那是我的梦想表白场景呢
Oh, man! That's my dream scenario!
我就只穿这个一小时
I'm only gonna do this for an hour,
给你们示范一下该怎么卖
to show you how it's done,
之后我就不干了
And then I'm out.
这是你们的梦想 不是我的
This is your dream, not mine.
小蛋糕 免费的小蛋糕
Cupcakes! Free cupcakes!
来嘛 尝一个
Come on, get 'em!
要趁热吃哦
Get 'em while they're hot!